[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "title": "Memory Items",
    "CardStack": [
      {
      "id": 0,
      "Front": "Cabin Altitude Hi",
      "Back": "Oxygen Masks - Don w/ 100% Oxygen, Crew Communications - Establish",
      },
      {
      "id": 1,
      "Front": "Engine Abnormal Start",
      "Back": "Affected Engine: Start/Stop Selector - STOP",
      },
      {
      "id": 2,
      "Front": "Smoke Evacuation",
      "Back": "Oxygen Masks: Don Emergency, Crew Communication: Establish, Pressurization Dump: Push In",
      },
      {
      "id": 3,
      "Front": "Smoke/Fire/Fumes",
      "Back": "Oxygen Masks: Don with 100% oxygen, Crew Communication: Establish",
      },
      {
      "id": 4,
      "Front": "Batt 1 (2) Overtemp",
      "Back": "Associated Battery: OFF",
      },
      {
      "id": 5,
      "Front": "Jammed Control Wheel - Roll",
      "Back": "Aileron Disconnect Handle: Pull",
      },
      {
      "id": 6,
      "Front": "Jammed Control Column - Pitch",
      "Back": "Elevator Disconnect Handle: Pull",
      },
      {
      "id": 7,
      "Front": "Pitch Trim Runaway",
      "Back": "A/P Disconnect Button: Press and Hold, Pitch Trim Sys 1 & 2 Cutout Buttons: Push In",
      },
      {
      "id": 8,
      "Front": "Roll (Yaw) Trim Runaway",
      "Back": "A/P Disconnect Button: Press and Hold",
      },
      {
      "id": 9,
      "Front": "Steering Runaway",
      "Back": "Steer Disconnect Switch: Press. steer the airplane using differential braking and rudder.",
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "title": "Weight Limitations",
    "CardStack": [
        {
        "id": 0,
        "Front": "Max Ramp Weight - 76 PAX ",
        "Back": "85,870 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 1,
        "Front": "Max Takeoff Weight - 76 PAX",
        "Back": "85,517 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 2,
        "Front": "Max Landing Weight - 76 PAX",
        "Back": "74,957 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 3,
        "Front": "Max Zero Fuel Weight - 76 PAX",
        "Back": "69,886 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 4,
        "Front": "Max Ramp Weight - 70 PAX ",
        "Back": "85,540 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 5,
        "Front": "Max Takeoff Weight - 70 PAX",
        "Back": "85,098 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 6,
        "Front": "Max Landing Weight - 70 PAX",
        "Back": "74,957 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 7,
        "Front": "Max Zero Fuel Weight - 70 PAX",
        "Back": "69,467 lb"
        },
        {
        "id": 8,
        "Front": "Min Runway Width",
        "Back": "100 ft"
        },
        {
        "id": 9,
        "Front": "Wing Span",
        "Back": "93 ft 11 in"
        },
        {
        "id": 10,
        "Front": "Aircraft Length",
        "Back": "103 ft 11 in"
        },
        {
        "id": 11,
        "Front": "Tail Height",
        "Back": "32 ft 4 in"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "title": "Operational Limitations",
      "CardStack": [
        {
          "id": 0,
          "Front": "Max Operational Altitude",
          "Back": "41,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 1,
          "Front": "Max Takeoff & Landing Altitude",
          "Back": "8,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "Front": "Max Temperature Takeoff & Landing",
          "Back": "ISA + 35 C or 52 F"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "Front": "Min Temperature Takeoff & Landing",
          "Back": "-40 C"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "Front": "Runway Slope Limitation",
          "Back": "+/- 2%"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "Front": "Max Tailwind",
          "Back": "15 kts"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "Front": "Max Single Pack Operations",
          "Back": "31,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "Front": "Vmo SL - 8000 ft",
          "Back": "300"
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "Front": "Vmo 10,000 - Mach Transition",
          "Back": "320"
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "Front": "Mmo",
          "Back": "0.82"
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "Front": "VA",
          "Back": "240"
        },
        {
          "id": 11,
          "Front": "VLO extend",
          "Back": "250"
        },
        {
          "id": 12,
          "Front": "VLO retract",
          "Back": "3250"
        },
        {
          "id": 13,
          "Front": "VLE",
          "Back": "250"
        },
        {
          "id": 14,
          "Front": "V tire",
          "Back": "195"
        },
        {
          "id": 15,
          "Front": "V RAT Deploy Max",
          "Back": "Vmo/Mmo"
        },
        {
          "id": 16,
          "Front": "Vmin To provide Electrical Power (RAT)",
          "Back": "130"
        },
        {
          "id": 17,
          "Front": "Vb (below 10,000 ft)",
          "Back": "250"
        },
        {
          "id": 18,
          "Front": "Vb (10,000 ft and above)",
          "Back": "270/0.76M (whichever is lower)"
        },
        {
          "id": 19,
          "Front": "V wiper ops ",
          "Back": "250"
        },
        {
          "id": 20,
          "Front": "V window",
          "Back": "160"
        },
        {
          "id": 21,
          "Front": "Vfe 1",
          "Back": "230"
        },
        {
          "id": 22,
          "Front": "Vfe 2",
          "Back": "215"
        },
        {
          "id": 23,
          "Front": "Vfe 3",
          "Back": "200"
        },
        {
          "id": 24,
          "Front": "Vfe 4",
          "Back": "180"
        },
        {
          "id": 25,
          "Front": "Vfe 5",
          "Back": "180"
        },
        {
          "id": 26,
          "Front": "V FULL",
          "Back": "165"
        },
        {
          "id": 27,
          "Front": "Dry Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "38 kt"
        },
        {
          "id": 28,
          "Front": "Wet Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "31 kt"
        },
        {
          "id": 29,
          "Front": "Runway with Compacted Snow Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "20 kt"
        },
        {
          "id": 30,
          "Front": "Runway with Standing Water/Slush/Wet Snow/Dry Snow Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "18 kt"
        },
        {
          "id": 31,
          "Front": "Runway with Ice Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "12 kt"
        },
        {
          "id": 32,
          "Front": "Static Crosswind Max Crosswind",
          "Back": "30 kts"
        },
        {
          "id": 33,
          "Front": "Max Altitude for Flaps and Slats to be Extended",
          "Back": "20,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 34,
          "Front": "Enroute Altitude for Slats and Flaps",
          "Back": "Prohibited"
        },
        {
          "id": 35,
          "Front": "Min Spoiler Speed",
          "Back": "180 kts"
        },
        {
          "id": 36,
          "Front": "Flap Setting - Cat II Approach ",
          "Back": "Mandatory Flaps 5"
        },
        {
          "id": 37,
          "Front": "Missed Approach Flap Setting - Flaps Full",
          "Back": "Flaps 4"
        },
        {
          "id": 38,
          "Front": "Missed Approach Flap Setting - Flaps 5",
          "Back": "Flaps 2"
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "title": "System Limitations",
      "CardStack": [
        {
          "id": 0,
          "Front": "Min Battery Voltage",
          "Back": "22.5 V"
        },
        {
          "id": 1,
          "Front": "Max Engine Temp",
          "Back": "815 C"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "Front": "Min Operational Oil Pressure",
          "Back": "25 PSI"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "Front": "Engine Start on Ground Cranking Limit",
          "Back": "Start 1 & 2 - 90 Seconds On and 10 Seconds Off; Start 3 - 5 - 90 Seconds On and 5 Minutes Off"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "Front": "Engine Start in Flight Cranking Limit",
          "Back": "Start 1 & 2 - 120 Seconds On and 10 Seconds Off; Start 3 - 5 - 120 Seconds On and 5 Minutes Off"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "Front": "Dry Motoring Duty Cycle Limits",
          "Back": "Motoring 1 - 90 Seconds On and 5 Minutes Off; Motoring 2 - 5 - 30 Seconds On and 5 Minutes Off"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "Front": "After 5 sequential motoring cylcles, when can the process be repeated",
          "Back": "AFter a 15 minute cool down period."
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "Front": "Caution When performing an engine start with a tailwind (monitor N1 indication)",
          "Back": "When there is no positive increase of N1 indiction before starter cutout (50% N2), engine start must be aborted"
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "Front": "Is a takeoff with Automatic Takeoff Thrust Control System (ATTCS) OFF allowed?",
          "Back": "NO"
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "Front": "Max Fuel Capacity",
          "Back": "20,935 lb"
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "Front": "Max Fuel Imbalance",
          "Back": "794 lbs"
        },
        {
          "id": 11,
          "Front": "Min Fuel Tank Temperature",
          "Back": "-37 C"
        },
        {
          "id": 12,
          "Front": "When must Fuel Crossfeed be on OFF",
          "Back": "During Takeoff and Landing"
        },
        {
          "id": 13,
          "Front": "How long should you wait after the EICAS is energized to start the APU",
          "Back": "30 seconds"
        },
        {
          "id": 14,
          "Front": "Max amount of time to leave the airplane unattended with the APU running ",
          "Back": "5 minutes"
        },
        {
          "id": 15,
          "Front": "APU bleed and _____ cannout be used simultaneously",
          "Back": "HP Cart"
        },
        {
          "id": 16,
          "Front": "APU Starter Duty Cycle",
          "Back": "Start 1 & 2 - 60 Seconds Off; Start 3 - 5 Minutes Off"
        },
        {
          "id": 17,
          "Front": "APU Start Min Temperature",
          "Back": "-54 C"
        },
        {
          "id": 18,
          "Front": "APU Start Max Temperature",
          "Back": "ISA + 35 "
        },
        {
          "id": 19,
          "Front": "APU Start Max Altitude",
          "Back": "30,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 20,
          "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Min Temperature",
          "Back": "-54 C"
        },
        {
          "id": 21,
          "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Max Temperature",
          "Back": "ISA + 35"
        },
        {
          "id": 22,
          "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Max Altitude",
          "Back": "33,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 23,
          "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Max Altitude Electrical Generator Use",
          "Back": "33,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 24,
          "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Max Altitude Bleed Use",
          "Back": "15,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 25,
          "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Max Altitude Engine Start",
          "Back": "21,000 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 26,
          "Front": "Max Differential Pressure UP to 37,000 ft",
          "Back": "7.8 PSI"
        },
        {
          "id": 27,
          "Front": "Max Differential Pressure Above 37,000 ft",
          "Back": "8.4 PSI"
        },
        {
          "id": 28,
          "Front": "Max Differential Over Pressure",
          "Back": "8.8 PSI"
        },
        {
          "id": 29,
          "Front": "Max Differential Negative Pressure",
          "Back": "-0.5 PSI"
        },
        {
          "id": 30,
          "Front": "Max Differential Pressure T/O Landing",
          "Back": "0.2 PSI"
        },
        {
          "id": 31,
          "Front": "Min Reservoir Temp for Engine Start",
          "Back": "-18 C"
        },
        {
          "id": 32,
          "Front": "When must ENG Anti Ice be turned on MCDU",
          "Back": "OAT is from 5C to 10C and visible moisture up to 1700 ft AFE or when operating on wet, snowy, icy runways ramps, taxiways"
        },
        {
          "id": 33,
          "Front": "When must ALL Anti Ice be turned on MCDU",
          "Back": "OAT is less than 5C and visible moisture up to 1700 ft AFE or when operating on wet, snowy, icy runways ramps, taxiways"
        },
        {
          "id": 34,
          "Front": "Min Autopilot Engagement Height ",
          "Back": "400 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 35,
          "Front": "Min Autopilot Use Height",
          "Back": "50 ft"
        },
        {
          "id": 36,
          "Front": "Min Autopilot Use Height-Non precision approach",
          "Back": "MDA"
        },
        {
          "id": 37,
          "Front": "Speed at Which TAS, TAT, and SAT is valid",
          "Back": "Above 60 kts"
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "title": "All Limitations",
      "CardStack": [
        {
        "id": 0,
        "Front": "Cabin Altitude Hi",
        "Back": "Oxygen Masks - Don w/ 100% Oxygen, Crew Communications - Establish",
        },
        {
        "id": 1,
        "Front": "Engine Abnormal Start",
        "Back": "Affected Engine: Start/Stop Selector - STOP",
        },
        {
        "id": 2,
        "Front": "Smoke Evacuation",
        "Back": "Oxygen Masks: Don Emergency, Crew Communication: Establish, Pressurization Dump: Push In",
        },
        {
        "id": 3,
        "Front": "Smoke/Fire/Fumes",
        "Back": "Oxygen Masks: Don with 100% oxygen, Crew Communication: Establish",
        },
        {
        "id": 4,
        "Front": "Batt 1 (2) Overtemp",
        "Back": "Associated Battery: OFF",
        },
        {
        "id": 5,
        "Front": "Jammed Control Wheel - Roll",
        "Back": "Aileron Disconnect Handle: Pull",
        },
        {
        "id": 6,
        "Front": "Jammed Control Column - Pitch",
        "Back": "Elevator Disconnect Handle: Pull",
        },
        {
        "id": 7,
        "Front": "Pitch Trim Runaway",
        "Back": "A/P Disconnect Button: Press and Hold, Pitch Trim Sys 1 & 2 Cutout Buttons: Push In",
        },
        {
        "id": 8,
        "Front": "Roll (Yaw) Trim Runaway",
        "Back": "A/P Disconnect Button: Press and Hold",
        },
        {
        "id": 9,
        "Front": "Steering Runaway",
        "Back": "Steer Disconnect Switch: Press. steer the airplane using differential braking and rudder.",
        },
          {
          "id": 10,
          "Front": "Max Ramp Weight - 76 PAX ",
          "Back": "85,870 lb"
          },
          {
          "id": 11,
          "Front": "Max Takeoff Weight - 76 PAX",
          "Back": "85,517 lb"
          },
          {
          "id": 12,
          "Front": "Max Landing Weight - 76 PAX",
          "Back": "74,957 lb"
          },
          {
          "id": 13,
          "Front": "Max Zero Fuel Weight - 76 PAX",
          "Back": "69,886 lb"
          },
          {
          "id": 14,
          "Front": "Max Ramp Weight - 70 PAX ",
          "Back": "85,540 lb"
          },
          {
          "id": 15,
          "Front": "Max Takeoff Weight - 70 PAX",
          "Back": "85,098 lb"
          },
          {
          "id": 16,
          "Front": "Max Landing Weight - 70 PAX",
          "Back": "74,957 lb"
          },
          {
          "id": 17,
          "Front": "Max Zero Fuel Weight - 70 PAX",
          "Back": "69,467 lb"
          },
          {
          "id": 18,
          "Front": "Min Runway Width",
          "Back": "100 ft"
          },
          {
          "id": 19,
          "Front": "Wing Span",
          "Back": "93 ft 11 in"
          },
          {
          "id": 20,
          "Front": "Aircraft Length",
          "Back": "103 ft 11 in"
          },
          {
          "id": 21,
          "Front": "Tail Height",
          "Back": "32 ft 4 in"
          },
          {
            "id": 22,
            "Front": "Max Operational Altitude",
            "Back": "41,000 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 23,
            "Front": "Max Takeoff & Landing Altitude",
            "Back": "8,000 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 24,
            "Front": "Max Temperature Takeoff & Landing",
            "Back": "ISA + 35 C or 52 F"
          },
          {
            "id": 25,
            "Front": "Min Temperature Takeoff & Landing",
            "Back": "-40 C"
          },
          {
            "id": 26,
            "Front": "Runway Slope Limitation",
            "Back": "+/- 2%"
          },
          {
            "id": 27,
            "Front": "Max Tailwind",
            "Back": "15 kts"
          },
          {
            "id": 28,
            "Front": "Max Single Pack Operations",
            "Back": "31,000 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 29,
            "Front": "Vmo SL - 8000 ft",
            "Back": "300"
          },
          {
            "id": 30,
            "Front": "Vmo 10,000 - Mach Transition",
            "Back": "320"
          },
          {
            "id": 31,
            "Front": "Mmo",
            "Back": "0.82"
          },
          {
            "id": 32,
            "Front": "VA",
            "Back": "240"
          },
          {
            "id": 33,
            "Front": "VLO extend",
            "Back": "250"
          },
          {
            "id": 34,
            "Front": "VLO retract",
            "Back": "3250"
          },
          {
            "id": 35,
            "Front": "VLE",
            "Back": "250"
          },
          {
            "id": 36,
            "Front": "V tire",
            "Back": "195"
          },
          {
            "id": 37,
            "Front": "V RAT Deploy Max",
            "Back": "Vmo/Mmo"
          },
          {
            "id": 38,
            "Front": "Vmin To provide Electrical Power (RAT)",
            "Back": "130"
          },
          {
            "id": 39,
            "Front": "Vb (below 10,000 ft)",
            "Back": "250"
          },
          {
            "id": 40,
            "Front": "Vb (10,000 ft and above)",
            "Back": "270/0.76M (whichever is lower)"
          },
          {
            "id": 41,
            "Front": "V wiper ops ",
            "Back": "250"
          },
          {
            "id": 42,
            "Front": "V window",
            "Back": "160"
          },
          {
            "id": 43,
            "Front": "Vfe 1",
            "Back": "230"
          },
          {
            "id": 44,
            "Front": "Vfe 2",
            "Back": "215"
          },
          {
            "id": 45,
            "Front": "Vfe 3",
            "Back": "200"
          },
          {
            "id": 46,
            "Front": "Vfe 4",
            "Back": "180"
          },
          {
            "id": 47,
            "Front": "Vfe 5",
            "Back": "180"
          },
          {
            "id": 48,
            "Front": "V FULL",
            "Back": "165"
          },
          {
            "id": 49,
            "Front": "Dry Max Crosswind",
            "Back": "38 kt"
          },
          {
            "id": 50,
            "Front": "Wet Max Crosswind",
            "Back": "31 kt"
          },
          {
            "id": 51,
            "Front": "Runway with Compacted Snow Max Crosswind",
            "Back": "20 kt"
          },
          {
            "id": 52,
            "Front": "Runway with Standing Water/Slush/Wet Snow/Dry Snow Max Crosswind",
            "Back": "18 kt"
          },
          {
            "id": 53,
            "Front": "Runway with Ice Max Crosswind",
            "Back": "12 kt"
          },
          {
            "id": 54,
            "Front": "Static Crosswind Max Crosswind",
            "Back": "30 kts"
          },
          {
            "id": 55,
            "Front": "Max Altitude for Flaps and Slats to be Extended",
            "Back": "20,000 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 56,
            "Front": "Enroute Altitude for Slats and Flaps",
            "Back": "Prohibited"
          },
          {
            "id": 57,
            "Front": "Min Spoiler Speed",
            "Back": "180 kts"
          },
          {
            "id": 58,
            "Front": "Flap Setting - Cat II Approach ",
            "Back": "Mandatory Flaps 5"
          },
          {
            "id": 59,
            "Front": "Missed Approach Flap Setting - Flaps Full",
            "Back": "Flaps 4"
          },
          {
            "id": 60,
            "Front": "Missed Approach Flap Setting - Flaps 5",
            "Back": "Flaps 2"
          },
          {
            "id": 61,
            "Front": "Min Battery Voltage",
            "Back": "22.5 V"
          },
          {
            "id": 62,
            "Front": "Max Engine Temp",
            "Back": "815 C"
          },
          {
            "id": 63,
            "Front": "Min Operational Oil Pressure",
            "Back": "25 PSI"
          },
          {
            "id": 64,
            "Front": "Engine Start on Ground Cranking Limit",
            "Back": "Start 1 & 2 - 90 Seconds On and 10 Seconds Off; Start 3 - 5 - 90 Seconds On and 5 Minutes Off"
          },
          {
            "id": 65,
            "Front": "Engine Start in Flight Cranking Limit",
            "Back": "Start 1 & 2 - 120 Seconds On and 10 Seconds Off; Start 3 - 5 - 120 Seconds On and 5 Minutes Off"
          },
          {
            "id": 66,
            "Front": "Dry Motoring Duty Cycle Limits",
            "Back": "Motoring 1 - 90 Seconds On and 5 Minutes Off; Motoring 2 - 5 - 30 Seconds On and 5 Minutes Off"
          },
          {
            "id": 67,
            "Front": "After 5 sequential motoring cylcles, when can the process be repeated",
            "Back": "AFter a 15 minute cool down period."
          },
          {
            "id": 68,
            "Front": "Caution When performing an engine start with a tailwind (monitor N1 indication)",
            "Back": "When there is no positive increase of N1 indiction before starter cutout (50% N2), engine start must be aborted"
          },
          {
            "id": 69,
            "Front": "Is a takeoff with Automatic Takeoff Thrust Control System (ATTCS) OFF allowed?",
            "Back": "NO"
          },
          {
            "id": 70,
            "Front": "Max Fuel Capacity",
            "Back": "20,935 lb"
          },
          {
            "id": 71,
            "Front": "Max Fuel Imbalance",
            "Back": "794 lbs"
          },
          {
            "id": 72,
            "Front": "Min Fuel Tank Temperature",
            "Back": "-37 C"
          },
          {
            "id": 73,
            "Front": "When must Fuel Crossfeed be on OFF",
            "Back": "During Takeoff and Landing"
          },
          {
            "id": 74,
            "Front": "How long should you wait after the EICAS is energized to start the APU",
            "Back": "30 seconds"
          },
          {
            "id": 75,
            "Front": "Max amount of time to leave the airplane unattended with the APU running ",
            "Back": "5 minutes"
          },
          {
            "id": 76,
            "Front": "APU bleed and _____ cannout be used simultaneously",
            "Back": "HP Cart"
          },
          {
            "id": 77,
            "Front": "APU Starter Duty Cycle",
            "Back": "Start 1 & 2 - 60 Seconds Off; Start 3 - 5 Minutes Off"
          },
          {
            "id": 78,
            "Front": "APU Start Min Temperature",
            "Back": "-54 C"
          },
          {
            "id": 79,
            "Front": "APU Start Max Temperature",
            "Back": "ISA + 35 "
          },
          {
            "id": 80,
            "Front": "APU Start Max Altitude",
            "Back": "30,000 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 81,
            "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Min Temperature",
            "Back": "-54 C"
          },
          {
            "id": 82,
            "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Max Temperature",
            "Back": "ISA + 35"
          },
          {
            "id": 83,
            "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Max Altitude",
            "Back": "33,000 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 84,
            "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Max Altitude Electrical Generator Use",
            "Back": "33,000 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 85,
            "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Max Altitude Bleed Use",
            "Back": "15,000 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 86,
            "Front": "APU Continuous Operation Max Altitude Engine Start",
            "Back": "21,000 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 87,
            "Front": "Max Differential Pressure UP to 37,000 ft",
            "Back": "7.8 PSI"
          },
          {
            "id": 88,
            "Front": "Max Differential Pressure Above 37,000 ft",
            "Back": "8.4 PSI"
          },
          {
            "id": 89,
            "Front": "Max Differential Over Pressure",
            "Back": "8.8 PSI"
          },
          {
            "id": 90,
            "Front": "Max Differential Negative Pressure",
            "Back": "-0.5 PSI"
          },
          {
            "id": 91,
            "Front": "Max Differential Pressure T/O Landing",
            "Back": "0.2 PSI"
          },
          {
            "id": 92,
            "Front": "Min Reservoir Temp for Engine Start",
            "Back": "-18 C"
          },
          {
            "id": 93,
            "Front": "When must ENG Anti Ice be turned on MCDU",
            "Back": "OAT is from 5C to 10C and visible moisture up to 1700 ft AFE or when operating on wet, snowy, icy runways ramps, taxiways"
          },
          {
            "id": 94,
            "Front": "When must ALL Anti Ice be turned on MCDU",
            "Back": "OAT is less than 5C and visible moisture up to 1700 ft AFE or when operating on wet, snowy, icy runways ramps, taxiways"
          },
          {
            "id": 95,
            "Front": "Min Autopilot Engagement Height ",
            "Back": "400 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 96,
            "Front": "Min Autopilot Use Height",
            "Back": "50 ft"
          },
          {
            "id": 97,
            "Front": "Min Autopilot Use Height-Non precision approach",
            "Back": "MDA"
          },
          {
            "id": 98,
            "Front": "Speed at Which TAS, TAT, and SAT is valid",
            "Back": "Above 60 kts"
          },
      ]
    }
]
